http://www.insightww.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | InsightWW
Contact Us • Login • Live Chat HomeWorkforce SolutionsIndustry SolutionsLearn MoreAbout UsContact UsBlog
Privacy PolicyHome/Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Sara Gillard
2020-03-31T17:43:20+00:00 PRIVACY POLICY   Last update 3/22/2020 INTRODUCTION Insight Worldwide, Inc. (“we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users (“user” or “you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our website www.insightww.net and www.insightww.com. Please read this privacy policy carefully. Your information is shared with our customers for application and/or employment record keeping and/or tracking purposes only. We will never sell, rent, or trade your Personally Identifiable Information. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the “Last Updated” date of this Privacy Policy. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Site, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of each such change or modification. You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted. COLLECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION We may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we may collect on the Site includes: Personal Data Personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, telephone number, and demographic information, such as your age, gender that you voluntarily give to us when you choose to participate in various activities related to the Site, such as completing an online assessment or training. Derivative Data Information our servers automatically collect when you access the Site, such as your IP address, your browser type, your operating system, your access times, and the pages you have viewed directly before and after accessing the Site. (If you are using our mobile application, this information may also include your device name and type, your operating system, your phone number, your country, your likes and replies to a post, and other interactions with the application and other users via server log files, as well as any other information you choose to provide.) Mobile Device Data Device information, such as your mobile device ID, model, and manufacturer, and information about the location of your device, if you access the Site from a mobile device. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION We may use information collected about you via the Site to:  Assist law enforcement and respond to subpoena.  Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis for use internally or with third parties.  Email you regarding your survey, assessment or training.  Perform other business activities as needed.  Respond to customer service requests. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION We may share information we have collected about you in certain situations. Your information may be disclosed as follows: By Law or to Protect Rights If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation. This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Third-Party Service Providers We may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, email delivery, hosting services, and customer service. Sale or Bankruptcy If we reorganize or sell all or a portion of our assets, undergo a merger, or are acquired by another entity, we may transfer your information to the successor entity. If we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, your information would be an asset transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that the transferee may decline honor commitments we made in this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the actions of third parties with whom you share personal or sensitive data, and we have no authority to manage or control third-party solicitations. If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly. TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES Cookies and Web Beacons We may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on the Site to help customize the Site and improve your experience. When you access the Site, your personal information is not collected through the use of tracking technology. Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. You can remove or reject cookies, but be aware that such action could affect the availability and functionality of the Site. You may not decline web beacons. However, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or by modifying your web browser’s settings to notify you each time a cookie is tendered, permitting you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. Website Analytics We may also partner with selected third-party vendors (such as Adobe Analytics, Clicktale, Clicky, Cloudfare, Crazy Egg, Flurry Analytics, Google Analytics,Heap Analytics, Inspectlet, Kissmetrics, Mixpanel, Piwik, and others), to allow tracking technologies and remarketing services on the Site through the use of first party cookies and third-party cookies, to, among other things, analyze and track users’ use of the Site, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. By accessing the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by these third-party vendors. You are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them directly for responses to your questions. We do not transfer personal information to these third-party vendors. However, if you do not want any information to be collected and used by tracking technologies, you can visit the third-party vendor or the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool. You should be aware that getting a new computer, installing a new browser, upgrading an existing browser, or erasing or otherwise altering your browser’s cookies files may also clear certain opt-out cookies, plug-ins, or settings. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES The Site may contain links to third-party websites and applications of interest, including advertisements and external services, that are not affiliated with us. Once you have used these links to leave the Site, any information you provide to these third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of your information. Before visiting and providing any information to any third-party websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect the privacy of your information. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other sites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Site. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your personal information. While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the personal information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorized parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you provide personal information. POLICY FOR CHILDREN We do not knowingly solicit information from or market to children under the age of 13. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us using the contact information provided below. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this Privacy Policy./Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. If you set the DNT signal on your browser, we will respond to such DNT browser signals. CONTACT US To obtain a copy of your personal information, request deletion of eligible personal information we have saved, or if you have any other questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: Insight Worldwide, Inc. PO Box 4108 Salem, OR 97302 888-314-8908 privacy@insightww.com  1-888-314-8908 Home |Contact Us |Sitemap |Privacy Policy© 2020 Insight Worldwide, Inc. All Rights Reserved
Subscribe
Subscribe!Subscribe here to our insightful and timely articles covering topics on hiring and workforce issues and solutions.By submitting this information you are agreeing to receive information from Insight Worldwide, Inc. via email. Your information will not be shared with third party organizations.
*All fields are required * Company
* Name
* Title
* Business E-mail
* Your Message
. HomeWorkforce SolutionsIndustry SolutionsLearn MoreAbout UsContact UsBlog
